A Guide to the Records of the Arlington Heritage Alliance, Inc., 1976-2006
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
Records of the Arlington Heritage Alliance, Inc., 1976-2006
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
RG 175
27 boxes.
Arlington Heritage Alliance
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Gail Baker in 2008 and 2009, and Vic Muniec in 2010.
Historical Information
The Arlington Heritage Alliance was incorporated as a nonprofit corporation in 1989 "to work for the preservation and creative uses of sites within Arlington County, Virginia, which are of historical, architectural, cultural, natural, and national significance." They cooperate with the Arlington County Historical Society and the County Historical Affairs and Landmark Review Board (HALRB).
They are now known as Preservation Arlington; their website is www.preservationarlington.org.
Scope and Content
The files of the Arlington Heritage Alliance, Inc., a private, nonprofit organization, consist of 11.26 linear feet and cover the time period from 1976 to 2006, with most of the materials dating 1988-2003.
The collection is arranged into six series. Series 1 is the files of the Board of Operation including its records of incorporation, its organization, minutes of the annual meetings and board of directors, by-laws, and correspondence files (later called Chronological Files). Membership files are in Series 2, and Programs, Tours and Special Events (including garden tours, heritage walks, programs, and a preservation dinner) are in Series 3. Series 4, Issues, comprises the bulk of the collection and are subject-oriented files including the Abingdon plantation, the designation of Buckingham as an historic district, Lawyers' Row, Fort C.F. Smith, Fort Ethan Allen, and the Columbia Pike Initiative. Series 5, Publications and Public Relations, includes brochures and press releases.
Series 6, Audio-Visual Materials, contains an extensive photograph collection. There are almost 400 slides of historic buildings, commercial districts, schools and other places of interest in Arlington County, most taken by Vic Muniec. A grant from the Bell Atlantic Corporation enabled the Alliance to document and photograph the Lawyers' Row buildings before they were demolished in 1990.
Additional files from Victor E. Muniec, American Heritage Alliance (AHA), were donated in 2010. Victor Muniec and his wife, Judith Priestley Muniec, were founding members of the AHA and were lifelong advocates of historic preservation. These were added to RG 175 as Series 7, Victor E. Muniec Files. Subseries 1 are AHA files, Subseries 2 are files on Arlington County, Subseries 3 are files on Virginia and the Washington, DC, area, Subseries 4 is related to Historic Preservation, and Subseries 5 is miscellaneous publications. Included with this acquisition were many photographs, many of which were prints of slides in the previous donation. These make up Subseries 6. If the photograph had a corresponding slide, the number on the slide was also used on the photograph.
Arrangement
The Arlington Heritage Alliance (AHA) had provided a list of their files. The order and division of the files are substantially the same as the AHA - that is, the series names are identical to the ones used by AHA with a few exceptions. Some extensive files were separated into subject files and further divided chronologically, such as the ones on Buckingham, Clarendon, and Fort C.F. Smith. File names are in alphabetical order and then chronological order. The pins and VHS videotape in Series 6 have been filed in a separate Artifacts Box. Some folders in this collection have photographs or negatives. Files with photographs have an asterisk [*} after the title and files with negative have a double asterisk [**] after the title.
The slides were organized by subject with some rearrangement to keep that order. Unknown and unidentified slides are at the end of the file. Appendix I is a list of the slides in a spreadsheet. Appendix II is a list of photos with file names provided by the archivist.
Some of the Vic Muniec files were organized in binders and those headings were retained. Other files were loose and named as labeled. They were then organized by the archivist in subject order, and then within those subjects, chronologically.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Related Record Groups are Record Group 22, Records of Arlington County Historical Boards and Commissions (including the HALRB), Record Group 30, Historic Neighborhood and Building Reports, and Photograph Collection 230, Arlington Historical Society Photographs.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Historic preservation -- United States.; Arlington (Va.); Arlington County (Va.)
Contents List
- Board of Operations
  - Subject Files
    - Action Plan, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Annual Report, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Annual Report, 1998-99 (Box 1)
    - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
    - Annual Report, 2000-01 (Box 1)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Board of Directors, 1989-1998 (Box 1)
    - Board of Directors, Biographies, 1992-2002 (Box 1)
    - Board of Directors, Job Descriptions, 1991-1993 (Box 1)
    - Board of Directors, Survey 1994 (Box 1)
    - Board Retreat, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Committees, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Formulation documents, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
    - IRS, 1989-1995 (Box 1)
    - Maps (Box 1)
    - Nominating Committee, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Northern Virginia Historic Resources (Box 1)
    - Volunteer Hours Log (Box 1)
  - Bylaws
    - Bylaws, Current, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Bylaws, Old, 1990-1993 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence Files
    - Correspondence, 1989-90 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1991-92 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1993-95 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, January-April 2000 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, May-July 2000 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, August-September 2000 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, October 2000 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, November 2000 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, December 2000 (Box 3)
    - Chronological Files, January-February 2001 (Box 3)
    - Chronological Files, March 2001 (Box 3)
    - Chronological Files, April 2001 (Box 3)
    - Chronological Files, May 2001 (Box 3)
    - Chronological Files, June 2001 (Box 3)
    - Chronological Files, July-September 2001 (Box 4)
    - Chronological Files, October-December 2001 (Box 4)
    - Chronological Files, January-February 2002 (Box 4)
    - Chronological Files, March 2002 (Box 4)
    - Chronological Files, April 2-14, 2002 (Box 4)
    - Chronological Files, April 15-30, 2002 (Box 4)
    - Chronological Files, May 2002 (Box 4)
    - Chronological Files, June 2002 (Box 5)
    - Chronological Files, July 2002 (Box 5)
    - Chronological Files, August-September 2002 (Box 5)
    - Chronological Files, October-November 2002 (Box 5)
    - Chronological Files, December 2002 (Box 5)
    - Chronological Files, January 2003 (Box 5)
    - Chronological Files, February 2003 (Box 5)
    - Chronological Files, March 2003 (Box 5)
    - Chronological Files, April-May 2003 (Box 5)
  - Minutes
    - Minutes, 1989-1991 * (Box 6)
    - Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 6)
    - Minutes, 1994-1999 (Box 6)
    - Minutes, 2000-2003 (Box 6)
  - Meetings
    - Meeting Attendance, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Meeting Schedule, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Planning
    - Development and New Project Ideas (Box 6)
    - Develop/Outreach Ideas, 1990-1994 (Box 6)
    - Management for Nonprofit Organizations, 1990-1993 (Box 6)
- Membership
  - Charter Membership, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Mailing Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Membership, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Membership, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Membership, 1990-2004 (Box 7)
  - Membership Drive, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Membership Drive, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Membership Form (Box 7)
  - Membership Responses, November 1998 (Box 7)
- Programs, Tours, Special Events
  - Awards, 1991-1999 * (Box 7)
  - Calendar, 1995 (Box 7)
  - County Fair, 1992-1994 * (Box 7)
  - Dream of Arlington (Box 7)
  - Events, 1989-2002 (Box 7)
  - Farmers, Raiders and Entertainers, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Fund Raiser, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Garden Tour, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Garden Tour, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Heritage Festival, 1990 * (Box 8)
  - Heritage Festival, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Heritage Walks, 1991-1993 (Box 8)
  - Holiday Party, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Jacobs Castle Tour, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Lecture Series, 1992-1997 (Box 8)
  - NTHP Garden Apartment Tour, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Neighborhood Survey, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Oral History Program, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Preservation Dinner, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Preservation Dinner, Finances, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Preservation Dinner, Sponsors, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Program - Researching a Property, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Programs, Fall 1993 (Box 8)
  - "We Live in Arlington" Project, 1995-1996 (Box 8)
  - World of Frank Lyon Tour, 2002 (Box 8)
- Issues
  - Abbey Mausoleum, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon, 1986-1989 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon, 1992-1995 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon Advisory Alert, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon - Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 9)
  - Abington - Legislation, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon - Press, 1989-1991 (Box 9)
  - Abingdon - Report - Historic Management Plan, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Agingdon - Report - Phase II Architecture Study, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Al's Motors/Gold's Gym, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Arlington Arts Center, 1989-1991 (Box 10)
  - Arlington Boathouse Coalition, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Arlington County School Bond, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Arlington History Center, 2000-2002 (Box 10)
  - Arlington Hospital Renovation, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Arlington National Cemetery, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Arna Valley (Box 10)
  - Bashing Arlington, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Boundary Stones, 1994-1995 (Box 10)
  - Boundary Stones Final Report, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
  - Buckingham, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Buckingham, April-July 1991 (Box 11)
  - Buckingham, August-November 1991 (Box 11)
  - Buckingham, January-August 1992 (Box 11)
  - Buckingham, September-November 1992 (Box 11)
  - Buckingham, January-April 1993 (Box 11)
  - Buckingham, May-September 1993 (Box 11)
  - Buckingham, 1994-2002 (Box 11)
  - Buckingham - Background Research (Box 11)
  - Buckingham - Historic Designation Recommendations, 1991-1993 (Box 12)
  - Buckingham - Housing Laboratory, 1938 (article from Architectural Record) (Box 12)
  - Buckingham - Lawsuits, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Buckingham - Quincy Street Extension Project, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Buckingham - Quincy Street Extension Project, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Buckingham - Quincy Street Extension Project, 1992-1994 (Box 12)
  - Buckingham Working Group, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Chain Bridge Road Sewer Line, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Chesapeake Bay Foundation - VA Nontidal Wetlands Act, 1999-2003 (Box 12)
  - Civil War Sites, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - Clarendon, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
  - Clarendon, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Clarendon, 1991-2007 (Box 13)
  - Clarendon Commercial District - NR Nomination, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Clarendon General Land Use Plan, 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - Clarendon Post Office, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Clarendon Sector Plan, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Claredon Sector Plan, Addendum A, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Clarendon Transportation Study, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Clarendon Urban Design Concept Plan, 1987-1989 (Box 13)
  - Clarendon Urban Design Concept Plan, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Clarendon Urban Design Concept Plan, Implementation Issues and Options, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Colonial Village, 1978-1989 (Box 14)
  - Colonial Village, 1990 * (Box 14)
  - Colonial Village, 1991 (Box 14)
  - Colonial Village, 1995-2002 * (Box 14)
  - Dawson Terrace, 1989-1991 (Box 14)
  - DeHart House (Box 14)
  - Drew School, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Eastman-Fenwick House, 1979-1992 (Box 14)
  - Endangered Property List, 1999-2000 (Box 14)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Appeal, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Appeal, 1991 (Box 15)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Background, 1986-1993 (Box 15)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Chronological File, 1986-1993 (Box 15)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 15)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - FOIA Issues, 1990-2000 (Box 15)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Hendry File, 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Hendry File, 1986-1989 (Box 15)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Hendry File, January-July 1990 (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Hendry File, July-December 1990 (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Hendry File, 1991-1999 (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Henry File (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - History, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Notes, Telcons, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Preliminary Information Form (PIF), 1995-1996 (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Preservation Plan, 1986-2003 (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Press/Publicity, 1986-2001 (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Standing, 1991 (Box 16)
  - Fort C. F. Smith - Water and Sewer Plans, 1989 (Box 16)
  - Fort Ethan Allen, Dog Exercise Area, 1999-2000 (Box 16)
  - Fort Ethan Allen, Dog Exercise Area, 2000-2001 (Box 17)
  - Fort Ethan Allen, Dog Exercise Area, 2001-2003 (Box 17)
  - Fort Ethan Allen, Dog Exercise Area, Press Clips, 2000-2002 (Box 17)
  - Fort Ethan Allen, Dog Exercise Area, Work Group, 2000-2001 (Box 17)
  - General Land Use Plan (Box 17)
  - George Washington Memorial Parkway, Historical and Archeological Study, 1990 (Box 17)
  - Glebe Road Widening, 1990 (Box 17)
  - HALRB (Historic Affairs & Landmark Review Board), 1990-1998 (Box 17)
  - Historic Preservation in Arlington - HALRB Paper, 2000 (Box 17)
  - Jacobs Castle, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Lawyers Row, 1986-1990 * (w/ floor plans) (Box 17)
  - Lawyers Row - Court House Sector Plan, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Lawyers Row - Grant, 1990 * (Box 18)
  - Lawyers Row - Notes (Box 18)
  - Maywood, 1989-2002 (Box 18)
  - Maywood - Courembis Appeal, 2000 (Box 18)
  - Maywood - Foley, 1992-1995 (Box 18)
  - Maywood - Press, 1990-2001 (Box 18)
  - Navy League Building, 2000-2001 (Box 18)
  - Navy League Buidling - HABS Report, 2001-2002 (Historic American Buildings Survey) (Box 18)
  - Neighborhood Historic Districts, 1988-1989 (Box 18)
  - Olmsted Property, 1999-2000 (Box 18)
  - Open Space* (includes Open Space Master Plan Locator Map, Feb 1994) (Box 19)
  - Parks Bond Referendum, 2000 (Box 19)
  - Pollard Gardens, 1990 (Box 19)
  - Potomac Palisades, 1990-1992 (Box 19)
  - Potomac River, 1999 (Box 19)
  - Preservation Issues, 1986-1993 (Box 19)
  - Robert Walker House (aka Gamble House), 2000 (Box 19)
  - Rosslyn-Ballston Corridor, 1982-2000 (Box 19)
  - SB514, 1992 (Box 19)
  - Schools RFB Bid, 1990 * (Box 19)
  - Student Neighborhood Survey, 2000 (Intro to Historic Preservation Class, University of Virginia) (Box 19)
  - Swanson Middle School, 2002 (Box 19)
  - Tax Exemptions for Commercial Structures, 2000 (Box 19)
  - Virginia General Assembly, 1999-2000 (Box 19)
- Publications and Public Relations
  - All Mail Outs, 1990-1992 * (Box 20)
  - Brochure, 1991 (Box 20)
  - Clip Art (Box 20)
  - Fact Sheet, 2000 (Box 20)
  - Press, 1989-2001 (Box 20)
  - Press Clips, 1989-1991 (Box 20)
- Audio-Visual Materials
  - Slides
    - Arlington County historic sites, buidlings and houses (Box 20)
      - Civil Ware era fort - earth
      - Freedman's Village
      - Clarendon Station
      - Glencarlyn Station - historic
      - Colonial Williamsburg Maps - Hondius (1930-458)
      - Colonial Williamsburg Maps - Smith's Virginia (G1984-1)
      - Fort Ethan Allen - drawing of site
      - Washington National Airport, 1941
      - Abingdon
      - Arlington Courthouse - orginial (demolished 1960s)
      - Arlington Hall
      - Ball Sellers House - historic view
      - Fort Meyer - U.S. Wireless Station
      - Fort Meyer (?) - old airplane
      - 1915 Arlington County City Directory, Clarendon
      - Arlington County City Directory
      - 1924 Arlington County City Directory
      - 1924 Arlington County City Directory, ads
      - Arligton County City Directory
      - 1915, 1924 Arlington County City Directory
      - 1915 Arlington County City Directory
      - Elmwood Cemetery - plan and obituary notice from c. 1900
      - Freedman's Village brochure
      - 1790 Census of Hancock, Mass.
      - 1876 Atlas of Hancock, Mass.
      - 1812 Virginia inventory
      - Wills and inventory
      - Livingstone Heights brochure
      - Livingstone Heights brochure
      - Rucker Lumber brochure - Cape Cod colonial
      - Postcard - Washington City from Potomac Park
      - McAlester Guide
      - American Vernae. Des. - Jennings & Gottlieb - Hipped Cottage
      - Abbey Mausoleum - Postcard, 1991
      - Abbey Mausoleum, 1991
      - Abbey Mausoleum, 1991
      - Abingdon at National Airport, 1991
      - Abingdon at National Airport, 1991
      - Abingdon at National Airport, 1991
      - Abingdon at National Airport, 1991
      - Abingdon at National Airport, 1991
      - Alcova at 3435 8th Street S., c. 1860, 1991
      - Alcova at 3435 8th Street S., c. 1860, 1991
      - Alcova at 3435 8th Street S., c. 1860, 1991
      - Al's Motors at 3910 Wilson Blvd., 1991
      - Arlington Cemetery, 1991
      - Arlington Cemetery, 1991
      - Arlington Cemetery c. Fall 1986, 1991
      - Arlington Cemetery, gravesite of the Custis family 1991
      - View to Lee House and Arlington Cemetery from the Lincoln Memorial, 1991
      - Arlington Village, 1991
      - Arlington Village - front (Cleveland St. near Columbia Pike), 1991
      - Arlington Village - rear of units, 1991
      - Arlington Village - view of garden square, 1991
      - 801 Irving Street in Ashton Heights, 1991
      - 808 Irving Street in Ashton Heights, 1991
      - 807 Irving Street in Ashton Heights, 1991
      - 923 Ivy Street (Earthworks), in Ashton Heights, 1991
      - 632 Ivy Street in Ashton Heights, 1991
      - 3520 Pershing in Ashton Heights, 1991
      - Jackson Street bungalow in Ashton Heights, 1992
      - Auto World at 3000 10th Street, 1993
      - Auto World at 3000 10th Street, 1993
      - Ball Family Burial Ground Sign in 1814 at 3427 Washington Boulevard, 1991
      - Ball Sellers House, c. 1760, at 5620 3rd Street S., 1991
      - Ball Sellers House, c. 1760, at 5620 3rd Street S., 1991
      - Ball Sellers House, c. 1760, at 5620 3rd Street S., 1991
      - Ball-Carlin Cemetery, c. 1785, at 300 S. Kensington, 1991
      - Bop Peck Chevrolet Body Shop at Danville & Wilson Blvd. in Ballston, 1993
      - Peck Chevrolet in Ballston, 1991
      - Peck Chevrolet in Ballston, 1991
      - Ballston - view, 1991
      - Ballston - view, 1991
      - Barcroft Community House, c. 1907, at 800 S. Buchanan Street, 1991
      - Barcroft School, 1991
      - Barcroft School - detail of entry, 1991
      - Boulevard Manor at Wilson Blvd. and McKinley Rd., 1991
      - Brandymore Castle Site at N. Roosevelt Street and Four Mile Run, 1991
      - Brandymore Castle Site at N. Roosevelt Street and Four Mile Run, 1991
      - Brandymore Castle Site at N. Roosevelt Street and Four Mile Run, 1991
      - Brumbach Realty, "Homes of character" - modern view, 1991
      - Brumbach Realty, "Homes of character" - original view, 1991
      - Buckingham - Street view, 1991
      - Buckingham - Glebe Market, 1991
      - Buckingham - Entry view with fence, 1991
      - Buckingham apartments, 1991
      - Buckingham apartments, 1991
      - Buckingham - Street view, 1991
      - Buckingham apartments, 1991
      - Buckingham - pool building?, 1991
      - Buckingham apartments, 1991
      - Buckingham apartments, 1991
      - Buckingham apartments, 1991
      - Buckingham Detail of Door, 1991
      - Buckingham apartments, 1991
      - Buckingham apartments, 1991
      - Buckingham - street view, 1991
      - Buckingham - Market, 1991
      - Carlin Community Hall, c. 1892, at 5711 4th Street S., 1991
      - Cedars - view of barn from the house, 1992
      - Cedars - view of barn from the house, 1992
      - Cedars - riverfront, 1992
      - Cedars - riverfront, 1992
      - Cedars - portico, 1992
      - Cedars - portico/front, 1992
      - Cedars - end of wing facade, 1992
      - Cedars - rear facade, 1992
      - Cedars - rear facade, 1992
      - Cedars - barn-cum-house, 1992
      - Chain Bridge Heritage Walk, 1991
      - Chain Bridge Heritage Walk, 1991
      - Chain Bridge Heritage Walk, 1991
      - Chain Bridge Heritage Walk, 1991
      - Potomac River - view west from Chain Bridge, 1991
      - Potomac River - view east from Chain Bridge, 1991
      - Pimmit Run S. V. near Chain Bridge
      - Cherrydale Hardware, 1991
      - Washington Boulevard in Clarendon, 1990
      - Washington and Wilson Boulevards in the business district of Clarendon, 1991
      - Wilson Blvd, west to east, in the business district of Clarendon, 1991
      - Tombstones and monuments at Washington Blvd. and Highland in Clarendon, 1991
      - Island Park looking toward the Metro station in Clarendon, 1991
      - Clarendon, 1990
      - Clarendon, 1990
      - Kirby Motors at 3275 Wilson Blvds, c. 1937, in Clarendon, 1990
      - 3100 Clarendon Blvd. in Clarendon, 1990
      - Wilson Blvd. from west to east in Clarendon, 1990
      - Building detail on Washington Boulevard in Clarendon, 1990
      - The Old Dominion Building at 1101 N. Highland in Clarendon, 1990
      - Clarendon, 1990
      - Clarendon, 1990
      - Main Post Office in Clarendon, 1991
      - Vista from Highland Street to Baptist church in Clarendon, 1990
      - Washington Blvd. and Highland in Clarendon, 1991
      - Citizens Hall in Clarendon, 1990
      - Masonic Lodge, c. 1910, at 3193 Wilson Blvd. in Clarendon, 1990
      - Clarendon, 1990
      - Clarendon, 1990
      - Clarendon, 1990
      - Arlington Post Office, c. 1937, at 3118 Washington Blvd. in Clarendon, 1991
      - detail of the facade of the Arlington Post Office at 3118 Washington Blvd. in Clarendon, 1991
      - Dan Kain Building, c. 1941, at 3100 Washington Blvd. in Clarendon, 1991
      - Dan Kain Building, c. 1941, at 3100 Washington Blvd. in Clarendon, 1991
      - Dan Kain Building, c. 1941, at 3100 Washington Blvd. in Clarendon, 1991
      - Virginia ABC Store on N. Highland Street in Clarendon, 1990
      - Wilson Blvd. from east to west in the buisiness district of Clarendon, 1991
      - A festival in Clarendon, 1991
      - Detail of the roof of 3217 Washington Blvd. in Clarendon, 1990
      - 3100 Clarendon Blvd. in Clarendon, 1991
      - Signage of the Underwood Building in Clarendon, 1991
      - Wilson Blvd. in Clarendon, 1991
      - Garage at the NE cornder of Fillmore and 10th Street in Clarendon, 1993
      - 3000 10th Street and Washington Blvd. in Clarendon, 1993
      - Demolition of houses in Colonial Terrace Heights, 1990
      - Demolition of apartments in Colonial Terrace Heights, 1990
      - Houses to be demolished in Colonial Terrace Heights, 1990
      - Houses to be demolished in Colonial Terrace Heights, 1990
      - Garage to be demolished in Colonial Terrace Heights, 1990
      - Apartment demolition in Colonial Terrace Heights, 1990
      - Demolition in Colonial Terrace Heights, 1990
      - Colonial Village, 1990
      - Colonial Village, 1990
      - Queen's Lane and N. Rhodes Street, c. 1934, in Colonial Village, 1991
      - Queen's St. and N. Rhodes Street, c. 1934, in Colonial Village, 1991
      - Queen's St. and N. Rhodes Street, c. 1934, in Colonial Village, 1991
      - Columbia Pike, 1987
      - Columbia Pike near Fillmore, 1991
      - Detail of the Country Club Cleaners at 2616 Pershing, 1993
      - Tile work and drive-in of the Country Club Cleaners at 2616 Pershing, 1993
      - Courthouse Area, 1990